Gold is already sniffing out this
weakness. Right now, if the dollar were
to take out all these lows, then I might
have to reassess. This pattern does
somewhat look like the Bitcoin dominance
pattern to me
from from the prior cycle. Right? So, if
you go look at at Bitcoin. You're like,
"Why is he Why does he always work in
Bitcoin dominance?" But, if you look at
at Bitcoin dominance in
you know, over here, there was a period
where you had three lower lows, and then
you had a fourth slightly lower low, and
then we were back in business.
The reason I don't think this is what's
going to happen, and that I think it'll
be a higher low instead, is because this
included stablecoins. And if you exclude
stablecoins from the Bitcoin dominance
chart, which I think is a relevant
exercise to do in order to truly measure
like, you know, what it is we're we're
actually trying to measure, you'll
you'll see that it actually looks
completely different. Right? So, when
you look at it like this, you'll see
that it was a higher low.